Hi, I am Emily Larew.
We are now going to combine your six step going to all four corners with a freeze.
So, we have already learned our basic six step in the previous segment.
So, we are down.
What is going to happen is, is how you turn this, is you are going to turn on your fourth step.
So, this is one, two, three, four.
Now, what we are going to do is on five, six turn and face the first corner.
Five, six.
Repeat it to this side.
One, two, three, four.
Now I am going to face the back, five, six.
And that is how I turn.
Again.
One, two, three, four, what are we going to do?
Change on five.
Five, six.
And again; one, two, three, four, turn, five, six.
From here, is where we are going to break it down and on the fourth step get into our freeze.
So, we are back to the front.
We just did the four corners.
You go; one, two, three, four.
From here, put your hand down.
You are going to tip over and back up into your freeze.
Seven, eight.
And then, back down.
And, you can start the whole thing again, which we are going to do right now.
Ready?
Here we go.
So, we have got; one, two, three, four, five six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Back to the front, three, four, five, six.
One more, three, four, up, hold.
There you go.
And that is your six step, all four corners with a freeze.